<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Custom List</string>
    <string name="sample">sample</string>
    <string name="pastaIngredients">Pasta noodles
\nWater
\nSalt
\nSauce or ingredients for sauce
\nOptional toppings </string>
    <string name="pastaDesc">1 Boil a pot of water and add salt to taste.
\n2 Cook the pasta noodles according to the package instructions until al dente.
\n3 While the pasta is cooking, prepare the sauce or ingredients for the sauce in a separate pan.
\n4 Drain the cooked pasta and add it to the sauce.
\n5 Toss the pasta in the sauce until it is well coated.
\n6 Optional: Add any additional toppings or seasonings as desired.
\n7 Serve the pasta hot and enjoy your delicious homemade meal.</string>
    //maggi
    <string name="maggiIngredients">Maggi noodles
\nMaggi seasoning or flavoring sachet
\nWater
    </string>
    <string name="maggieDesc">1 Boil water in a pot.
\n2 Add the Maggi noodles to the boiling water.
\n3 Cook the noodles for about 2-3 minutes or until they are soft and tender.
\n4 Drain most of the water, leaving a little to mix with the seasoning.
\n5 Add the Maggi seasoning or flavoring sachet to the noodles and mix well.
\n6 Optional: You can also add cooked vegetables, eggs, or other toppings to enhance the flavor and nutritional value.
\n7 Serve the Maggi noodles hot and enjoy your quick and easy meal.</string>
    //cake
    <string name="cakeIngredients">Flour\nSugar\nEggs\nButter or oil\nBaking powder or baking soda\nMilk or water\nFlavorings (e.g., vanilla extract, almond extract)\nSalt (a pinch)</string>
    <string name="cakeDesc">1 Preheat oven.
\n2 Grease and flour cake pans.
\n3 Mix dry ingredients in a bowl.
\n4 Beat eggs and mix with melted butter/oil, milk/water, and flavorings in a separate bowl.
\n5 Combine dry and wet ingredients, mix until smooth.
\n6 Pour batter into pans.
\n7 Bake in preheated oven for specified time.
\n8 Cool in pans for 10 minutes, then transfer to wire rack to cool completely.
\n9 Frost and decorate.
\n10 Slice and enjoy!</string>
    //pancake
    <string name="pancakeIngredients">Flour
\nSugar (optional)
\nBaking powder
\nSalt
\nEggs
\nMilk
\nButter or oil (for cooking)
\nVanilla extract (optional)</string>
    <string name="pancakeDesc">1 Mix dry ingredients in a bowl.
\n2 In a separate bowl, mix wet ingredients.
\n3 Combine wet and dry ingredients, stir until just combined.
\n4 Heat a greased pan or griddle over medium heat.
\n5 Pour 1/4 cup of batter onto the pan for each pancake.
\n6 Cook until bubbles form on the surface, then flip and cook the other side until golden brown.
\n7 Remove from the pan and repeat with the remaining batter.
\n8 Serve warm with toppings of your choice.</string>
    //pizza
    <string name="pizzaIngredients">
        Pizza dough or pre-made pizza crust
\nPizza sauce or marinara sauce
\nCheese (mozzarella is commonly used)
\nToppings (such as pepperoni, mushrooms, onions, bell peppers, etc.)
\nOlive oil (for drizzling)
    </string>
    <string name="pizzaDesc">1 Preheat your oven to the highest temperature possible (usually around 475째F or 245째C).
\n2 Roll out or shape the pizza dough into your desired size and thickness.
\n3 Place the pizza dough on a greased or parchment-lined baking sheet or pizza stone.
\n4 Spread pizza sauce evenly over the dough, leaving a border for the crust.
\n5 Sprinkle shredded cheese evenly over the sauce.
\n6 Add your desired toppings, such as pepperoni, mushrooms, onions, bell peppers, etc.
\n7 Drizzle a little olive oil over the toppings.
\n8 Place the pizza in the preheated oven and bake for about 10-15 minutes, or until the crust is golden and the cheese is melted and bubbly.
\n9 Remove the pizza from the oven and let it cool for a few minutes before slicing and serving.</string>
    //burgers
    <string name="burgerIngredients">Ground beef (or alternative like turkey, chicken, or veggie patties)
\nHamburger buns
\nLettuce
\nTomato slices
\nOnion slices
\nPickles
\nCheese slices (optional)
\nCondiments (such as ketchup, mustard, mayonnaise)</string>
    <string name="burgerDesc">1 Preheat a grill or stovetop pan over medium-high heat.
\n2 Shape ground beef into patties, season with salt and pepper.
\n3 Cook the patties on the grill or pan, flipping once, until desired level of doneness (usually around 4-5 minutes per side for medium).
\n4 While the patties cook, lightly toast the burger buns.
\n5 Assemble the burger by placing the cooked patty on the bottom bun.
\n6 Add desired toppings like lettuce, tomato slices, onion slices, pickles, cheese, and condiments.
\n7 Place the top bun on the assembled burger.
\n8 Serve immediately and enjoy your delicious homemade burger!</string>
    //fries
    <string name="friesIngredients">Potatoes
\nCooking oil (such as vegetable or canola oil)
\nSalt</string>
    <string name="friesDesc">1 Preheat the oven to 425째F (220째C).
\n2 Peel and cut potatoes into desired fry shape (thin or thick).
\n3 Rinse the cut potatoes in cold water to remove excess starch.
\n4 Pat dry the potatoes using a kitchen towel or paper towels.
\n5 Toss the potatoes with cooking oil until evenly coated.
\n6 Arrange the potatoes in a single layer on a baking sheet.
\n7 Sprinkle salt over the potatoes.
\n8 Bake in the preheated oven for about 20-25 minutes, flipping once halfway through, until the fries are golden brown and crispy.
\n9 Remove from the oven and let them cool for a few minutes.
\n10 Serve the fries hot and enjoy them as a delicious side dish or snack</string>
</resources>